

# **Nguyen Thi Minh Hang**

Medical Representative

Date of birth: 2nd September, 1995

Gender: Female

Phone: 0982092417

Email: minhhang9g@gmail.com

Address: 9 Ha Ba Tuong Street, 12 Ward, Tan Binh District, Ho Chi

Minh City.

# **OBJECTIVE**

Firstly, I want to pass the interview and probationary period. Building a harmonious relationship with colleagues to achieve a high sale rate is another purpose that I want to obtain. Finally, if I have a chance I want to become a group manager after 1.5 to 2 years (from 3 to 5 members).

# **EDUCATION**

August 2014 - August 2019

#### **TAY DO UNIVERSITY**

Major: Pharmacy

Degree classification: Good, GPA: 2.96/4 (7.4/10)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

August 2018 - May 2019

#### **VOLUNTEER OF ENGLISH CLUB OF TAY DO UNIVERSITY**

Teaching Assistant

Main responsibilities:

- Supported the main teacher to teach pronunciation for students.
- Prepared lesson, content, game for the class.

Number: 30 to 40 students.

September 2014 - May 2019

#### **LEADER OF LEARNING GROUP**

Leader

Main responsibilities:

- Assigned exercises, presentations to meet deadline.
- Contacted teachers and leaders of another groups.

Number: 10 students

#### **ACTIVITIES**

October 2014 - October 2019

# TRUONG DAI HOC TAY DO

- Attended PUBLIC SPEAKING CONTEST 2018.
- Joined PROE CONTEST 2018.
- Studied Toeic, IELTS.
- A volunteer at the English Club of Tay Do University.

#### "BE PHARMACIST" COFFEE TALK CAN THO

Role: participant

- Learning experience, knowledge about Medical Representative.
- Developing soft skills and studying customer psychological

knowledge.

# **HONORS & AWARDS**

2018

- The Encourage prize of PUBLIC SPEAKING CONTEST 2018
- Second prize: Certificate of Video Championship (English Olympiad for Non English Major Students) honored by Viet Nam National University, Ha Noi, University of Languages and International Studies).
- IELTS 5.0
- TOEIC 555
- Soft skills certificate
- Information Technology Certification.